The holidays are better together.
Trolls Holiday in Harmony is a animation, fantasy,
family film directed by Sean Charmatz.
Queen Poppy plans the first annual Trolls Kingdom Secret Holiday
Gift Swap, but things don't go quite as expected.
Poppy (voice), played by Anna Kendrick.
Branch (voice), played by Justin Timberlake.
Tiny Diamond (voice), played by Kenan Thompson.
Rhyme-a-saurus (voice), played by Travis Scott.
Windbreeze (voice), played by Carol Burnett.
Barb (voice), played by Rachel Bloom.
Trolls: Holiday in Harmony is a 2021 American animated musical
Christmas special that premiered on NBC on November 26, 2021.
Based on DreamWorks Animation's Trolls franchise, this was the second one to be based on the franchise following Trolls Holiday, written and directed by Sean
Charmatz and Tim Heitz (in their official directorial debuts) and, as of 2025, the most recent television special from DreamWorks Animation.
A majority of the cast from the two movies reprise their respective roles, including Anna Kendrick, Justin Timberlake, Rachel Bloom, and Kenan
Thompson; likewise, Lauren Mayhew and Megan Hilty reprise their respective roles as Val Thundershock and Holly Darlin' from TrollsTopia.
The special features famous actress and comedian Carol
Burnett as the voice of Wind Breeze.
The film explores themes of holiday, musical, christmas special, short film.
The tone is lighthearted.